# **DENICE HARRIS**

Senior Graphic Design



Senior Graphic Design Specialist with 6+ years of experience managing design processes, from conceptualization to delivery. Skilled with Adobe Creative Suite (Illustrator, Photoshop, InDesign), Microsoft Office, and web design applications (Dreamweaver, HTML). Able to stretch the boundaries of web design and digital storytelling to help my client's brands stand out and grow.

### **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Arts, Communications Rochester Technology, Rochester NY Design GPA: 3.7/4.0 May 2015

## **KEY SKILLS**

- InDesign
- Illustrator
- Photoshop
- Figma

#### **ADDITIONAL SKILLS**

- Fluent in Spanish
- Infographic design
- Branding & identity

#### REFERENCE

Chloe Ramirez Senior Graphic Designer | Experion 150 West 25th St, New York, NY (636) 423-2759 c.ramirez@experion.com Chloe was my direct manager from March 2019 until November 2022.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

## Senior Graphic Design **Specialist**

2019 - Present

• Lead the design, development, and implementation of graphic, layout, and production communication materials while helping

clients cut costs by an average of 12%

Delegate tasks to a 7-member design team and provide counsel

on all aspects of the project

Assess all graphic materials created in-house to ensure the

quality and accuracy of their designs

Oversee design project budgets ranging from \$2,000 - \$25,000

Graphic Design Specialist

2017 - 2019

Stepping Stone Advertising, New

Experion, New York, NY

York, NY

Developed numerous marketing programs (logos, brochures, newsletters, infographics, presentations, and advertisements) and made sure they exceeded the expectations of our clients

Managed up to 5 projects or tasks at a given time and ensured our team met its weekly deadlines

• Consulted with clients on the most appropriate graphic design options based on their major marketing goals

Led design updates to modernize brand marketing, including a new color scheme and typography

Junior Graphic Designer Redfin Technologies, New Rochelle,

2015 - 2017

NY

 Worked with senior designers to develop unique product branding

Designed 30+ online advertisements to increase RedFin's brand awareness

 Created 15 original illustrations for a website redesign using Adobe Illustrator and Photoshop

# Dear Job Seeker,

We named this resume template "Quick" because of how fast it catches the eye. A unique full-page color scheme and headshot help your resume stand out from the crowd and communicates to employers that you're not afraid to take risks.

The "Quick" template is perfect when applying for jobs that aren't afraid to get creative, like those in design or social media.

If you're still struggling to write your resume, here are some free resources to help you put together a resume that shows employers you're the right person for the job:

Once you have a great resume, pair it with a convincing cover letter using our matching cover letter templates. Here are a few resources to help you write a cover letter that gives your application the boost it needs to land you an interview:

Best regards,

IMPORTANT: To delete the second page, right-click on the page and click "Delete Rows"

The Resume Genius Team